<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="permission_camera_rationale">Access to the camera is needed for detection</string>
    <string name="no_camera_permission">This application cannot run because it does not have the camera permission.  The application will now exit.</string>
    <string name="low_storage_error">Ocr dependencies cannot be downloaded due to low device storage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Ocr Detector Sample</string>
    <string name="ocr_header">Click &quot;Detect Text&quot; to detect text</string>
    <string name="read_text">Detect Text</string>
    <string name="auto_focus">Auto Focus</string>
    <string name="use_flash">Use Flash</string>
    <string name="ocr_success">Text read successfully</string>
    <string name="ocr_failure">No text captured</string>
    <string name="ocr_error">"Error reading text: %1$s"</string>
    <string name="warning_message">DO NOT rely only on this app to check food labels for allergies.
        This app is intended to be used only to help you double check a food label for allergies.
        The app creator is not responsible for any allergic reactions, injury, or death caused by using this app.
        By pressing the "I Accept" button below, you agree to the above terms.\n\n
        Point the camera toward the food label so the entire label is in view.
        Safe ingredients show up as green and potential allergy ingredients show up as red in larger font.\n\n
        Thank you for using Ingredients Scanner!</string>
    <string name="warning_accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="remove_allergy">Remove</string>
    <string name="allergy_input_hint">Type allergy here</string>
    <string name="add_allergy_button_text">Add</string>
    <string name="scan_label_button_text">Scan Label</string>
    <string name="contact_email_subject">Ingredients Scanner Inquiry</string>
    <string name="about_allergy_app">Allergy Label Checker is an Android app that allows people with allergies to easily check food ingredient labels with their phone.\n\n
    Instrcutions:\n
    1. Make sure you read and accept the warning stated when starting the app. Do NOT rely only on this app for checking food labels for your allergies.\n
    2. In the Allergy List menu item, enter your allergy into the text field by tapping on Type allergy here.\n
    3. Once you entered one allergy, click the blue ADD button to the right of where you entered your allergy.\n
    4. Your allergy will now show up in the list below. Continue steps 2-4 until all of your allergies have shown up in the list.\n
    \ta. To delete an allergy from the list, tap and hold on it.\n
    5. Click on Scan Label in the navigation window. If prompted, tap Allow to allow this app to access your device camera\n
    6. Point your device camera at a food ingredient label.\n
    \ta. Detected ingredients that are not contained in your allergy list show up in green (not an allergy).\n
    \tb. Detected allergies show up in red (detected allergies). If you see red text, you should avoid this food.\n
    7. To return to the menu, tap the back button on your phone.\n\n
    If you have questions or suggestions, tap the Contact button in the menu and send me an email.\n\n
    Thank you for using Ingredients Scanner!</string>
</resources>
